Chirag Pravin Waghela

chirag.waghela7594@gmail.com



+91-7208-1707-17



Chirag Waghela | Portfolio

OBJECTIVE

Hard-working individual with proficiency in HTML,CSS and JavaScript, as well as strong ability to communicate and work in a team effectively. 4 years experience of daily working on, writing, and reviewing codes, aiming to enhance the dynamic work of the company.

SKILLS

- **Technical** HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Wordpress, SCSS, Tailwind, Vue.js, PHP, Blade.
- **Professional** -Coaching, Time management.
- **Tools** Visual Code, Atom, Filezilla, SourceTress, Gitlab, Terminal, Figma, Zeplin.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Wohlig Transformation Private Limited, Mumbai, Senior SDE September 2023- Present

 Working on client side project which includes end to end dashboard integration using tech like Vue 3, Bootstrap, Primevue etc

Media.Net Software Services (India) Private Limited, Mumbai, UI Developer January 2019 – September 2023

- Developed an automated HTML/CSS generator to reduce the turnaround time for daily tasks using JavaScript.
- Developed and worked on Automated mailer system on organization level using technology like PHP and Google Sheet API.
- Involved in defining coding standards, code review and knowledge sharing sessions.
- Working closely and interacted with Business Developers to roll out daily tasks.
- Coaching and mentoring junior developers while regularly overseeing delivery of projects.
- Responsible for the development of multiple mobile responsive websites using WordPress.
- Actively worked on enhancing and improving existing products by designing, developing and rolling out new features.
- Developed JavaScript demos for multiple projects.
- Worked actively on internal projects in tight deadlines for delivery of premium UI designs.
- Working with premium clients for developing and delivering new features and requirements on a weekly

basis. Tech including wordpress, vue.js, tailwind css, html, css, javascript, Git.

NevonSolutions Pvt. Ltd, Mumbai, Frontend Developer October 2018 – December 2018

- Worked on multiple projects using HTML/CSS templates.
- Worked closely with the backend team for small task delivery of ASP.net projects.

EDUCATION

Bachelors of Information Technology 2017 Shah and Anchor Kutchhi Engineering College (Mumbai University) CGPI - 6.47

Diploma in Computer Engineering 2014 Shri Bhagubhai Mafatlal Polytechnic (Autonomous) - 64.97%

Higher Secondary Certificate 2010 St. Xavier's High School, Maharashtra State board. - 82.73%

PERSONAL DETAILS

D.O.B: 7th May 1994

Languages Proficiency: English, Gujarati, Hindi, Marathi